INFO:



Dmytro Hoi Python Developer

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com LinkedIn: dmytrohoi Telegram: @dmytrohoi

Site: hoid.dev

SUMMARY:

I've been programming in Python for almost three years. I worked on the following major tasks: creation of a quality control system for the Big Data/ML project (Python and JS); creating and maintaining a custom Python test framework based on Appium for a medical embedded project (complex medical device on Android); creation of bots for Telegram and Discord (Python, JS); creation of site parsing scripts (Python, JS, complex Regex); creation of Bash/zsh console scripts (e.g. site deploying, environment setup); contribution to open-source projects on GitHub (e.g. python-telegram-bot, aiogram); creation of plugins and a plugin loader for a game (Minecraft, Java, Jython); creation of a personal site (ReactJS, JS on Cloudflare Workers). I also teach Python and Basic Development courses at a famous IT school and write articles on well-known resources.

My personal projects are collected in hoid.dev/#projects.

Additional programming languages are: Javascript, sh, Ruby and Go (learning in progress). I finished studying Systems Analysis, including machine learning.

SKILLS:

- Languages: Python, JavaScript, Ruby, bash scripting, Go (learning in progress).
- Libraries/Frameworks: pytest, appium, jest, python-telegram-bot/aiogram, Flask, SQLAlchemy/Gino, requests, tkinter
- English-level: Intermediate (good reading and listening, but poor speaking skills)
- Tools: Git, SVN, adb, cron, Docker, venv/pipenv
- Other: zsh, HTML/CSS, SQL, Regex, GitHub, sr.ht, Ubuntu, Arch, Windows Details on my site: <u>hoid.dev</u>

ADDITIONALS SKILLS:

- Initiative, automation integration, and proactive
- Public speaking and teaching skills
- Writing articles (<u>habr.hoid.dev</u> | <u>devto.hoid.dev</u> | <u>blog.hoid.dev</u>)
- Also: SMM, PR, Poems writing

PERSONAL PROJECTS:

- <u>hi gain dev</u> personal programming blog
- <u>freelancehunt-api</u> framework for public API on Python (PyPI)
- <u>afilters.js</u> advanced filters for JS (<u>NPM</u>, <u>docs</u>)
- <u>pyplugins</u> plugin loader for the famous game on Java and Jython (Minecraft)
- <u>pelican-qsb</u> a tool for quickly building Pelican-based websites on Python (<u>PvPI</u>)
- other projects: bots (e.g. nurecraft-bot), scripts and programs with a GUI

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Company: Grid Dynamics

Position: Automation QA Engineer (02/2021 - now)

Info: Creation Quality Control system for Big Data/ML project (stack: flask, reactjs)

Company: GlobalLogic

Position: Automation QA Engineer (05/2019 - 02/2021)

Info: Implementation of a custom test framework for the embedded device on Android

(stack: Python, Appium, ADB, and pytest)

Company: Microbilt

Position: Site Scraping Script Developer (07/2018 - 05/2019)

Info: Programming with Regex and SQL. Python and Javascript automation scripting.

Company: National University of Radioelectronics

Position: Senior Assistant at Quality Assurance Department (06/2016 - 05/2017) **Info:** Creation and maintain of an internal quality assurance system (ISO:9001).

EDUCATION:



Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics

- Bachelor (2014 - 2018) Electronics - "Electronics devices and systems"

- Master (2018 - 2019) System Analysis - "Consolidated information"

DMYTRO HOI / Mar 2021 2/2

E-mail: me@dmytrohoi.com | LinkedIn: dmytrohoi | Site: hoid.dev

NOTE: Also my site is available at dmytrohoi.com